https://mrshrinkwrap.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY - for Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc.
Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of the online product catalog at this site. This policy may change from time to time so please re-visit this page periodically. Web sites, which are linked to this site may have different policies and Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
Disclosure and Use of Information: Any personal information you provide on this site may be used, held or shared only by Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. and its affiliates, associated companies, agents, distributors or others in the supply chain to fulfill your order and provide you services associated with products you purchase through this site. Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. will not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others outside of the Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. organization.
We may disclose information in special cases when we believe in good faith that such release is necessary to comply with law, to identify or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms of service, to enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. or others. Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. is global company and this site has users all over the world. Any information you give us through this site may be transmitted to servers outside the country where the information was entered, and may be used, stored and processed outside of the country where it was entered. We may use certain commercial information gathered from this site to compile demographic information about the users and use of this site.
Security: We will make our best effort to ensure the security of our system and will strive to protect any personal information you provide through this site. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee that all data transmitted over the Internet will be secure.
Ordering: When you place an order using Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc.'s online product catalog services, the credit card information you submit will be transmitted in a secured format using secure server software (SSL) which encrypts this information. Of course, your credit card information will be submitted to the credit card institution for processing.
Cookies: A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server to be stored on your hard drive that allows easier access the next time the same page is visited. For example, a cookie is sent when you register or sign in to this site. With your consent, cookies can store information from forms you fill out at this site to create a user profile so that you do not have to re-enter the information each time you visit. Your browser can probably be set to notify you whenever a cookie is received so you can decide whether or not to accept it.
Sending e-mail to us: You may send us e-mail at csr@domain.com . We may keep a record of e-mail we receive.
IP Addresses: An IP address is a number which is used to identify computers so that data such as Web pages you request can be sent to you. Our Web server automatically collects IP addresses for purposes of administering our system and to help us diagnose problems with our server.
Consent: By using the Mr Shrinkwrap, Inc. online product catalog to order products, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us.
Users: Under the Age of 13 If you are under the age of 13, do not provide any personally identifiable information on this site without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian.
Back to top of page
Follow us on
Facebook
Twitter
Google
Main Office, Shipping & Receiving:
660 13th Avenue Building 4 Prospect Park, PA 19076   Get Directions Here
Save on Shipping, Pick-Up is Free! Please place order online or by phone prior to your arrival
Mailing Address:
